Isn't this view awful?
Sea, mountains, sun, sky.
It's a perfect view.
Here we are!
I came to Shizuoka to fish!
Yes, yes!
It's 5 o'clock in the morning.
It's morning!
Today I want to go fishing in Shizuoka on my father's boat!
I got a fishing rod on Youtube the last time I was here!
So I'd like to use it to catch some sea bream today.
I haven't fished in about three months!
It's a beautiful day for fishing!
It's a nice day for fishing.
This is the sea where I've been fishing since I was really young.
That's Mt Fuji!
I always lived my life looking at Mt Fuji. Fuji when I was in Shizuoka.
Today, my goal is to catch a fish of 50 cm, but I've only caught fish of 30 cm.
I'd like to catch a huge fish, a huge tie, over 50 cm.
I caught a tai at Sakura Meets the other day.
It was really a local fish, not even 10 cm long,
I kind of want to catch a tie that's about 50 centimetres today.
I'll do my best, I'll do my best.
This is a sao called a koga that I bought the other day,
It's very light and thin.
I paid a very good price for it.
I hope you can take me today.
Staff, staff, staff, staff.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
Put it in about an eighth.
Street.
And...
My good? Just cut the tail off and stab it through the arse.
Hey, watch it, get it right.
I did it the other day.
I'll make sure it doesn't come off.
It'll look like this.
Do you see what I mean?
Yes. This fishing... off the hook! It's already tangled. Wait a minute, it was already tangled.
No, we have to start from the hook.
I don't know where the hook is.
So I'm tangled up and done.
No, no, no, you don't know if it's tangled.
He's pissed.
All right, let's go.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm pissed off.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm not involved.
Oh, wow.
That's a nice sound.
I got there without getting tangled up.
20 metres.
Oh, 20 metres.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
About 20 is fine.
Yes, do the other one, do the other one.
Yes, yes, yes.
Scary, scary, scary.
Scary.
You can have whichever one catches.
You don't wait for me.
What am I supposed to do?
Thai fishing is just waiting to catch a fish like this.
All you can do is wait to catch a fish.
I'll change the bait again and again.
I've got no choice but to change the bait
I'm going to fish in a wait-and-see style this time.
I'd really like to do something about it, but...
But there's a tie at a depth of 20 metres.
I'm going to fish in a watch-and-see style, without moving.
It's dazzling.
I wonder...
Can you catch a tie with a prawn?
I don't know.
I'm sure they've already run out of prawns
Try lifting it once.
Lift it slowly.
How do you take this?
Lift it up.
How do you take it?
Take it like this.
Like this.
Put it like this.
I see.
No, put it down like this.
It's not here. We have to put more in.
It's not broken.
I'll put it here.
I don't know how many fish are out there today, but I hear there's a lot.
Which ones are Thai hands?
This one.
This one?
The one down there.
You mean this one?
The one that looks like water down there? Is this the water from Thailand? The one that looks like water down there.
This?
Is this Thailand?
Yes, that's it.
So we're fishing at 20 metres, watching the waves.
I see.
They're not coming at all.
Tye, tye, they're not coming.
This way, too.
It's been two hours.
I can't catch anything at all.
I don't know.
There's no sign of any fish.
Oh...
No bait.
Shrimps!
I hate it when I can't catch anything.
Can't I just use the other rod and reel it in like a normal fishing rod?
No.
Why not?
Because this fishing...
If we don't catch anything, we won't catch anything, will we?
Nothing.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
What?
See, I knew I caught something.
It's a bit awkward.
I told you he was eating something.
Well, I've caught a grouper.
Cute. Let's move.
You can't catch anything here.
Oh, I've got it on clean.
It's a good 35 metres.
That's a lot of depth, isn't it?
All the way down.
What's the big deal about fishing?
I wonder.
It's so peaceful.
It's like a tranquil time.
I like it a lot, and I've been busy rehearsing for gigs and stuff,
I forgot about the ballet, but now I remember.
Fishing on the first day
I'm here.
Is this thing pulling?
I'll wind it up. I don't know.
I don't know.
What?
Are there any fish in there?
Maybe.
What's this? Could be a leatherfish.
It could be a sea bream.
It's a tie! It's tiny, but...
It's tiny, but it's tiny! Tiny!
You forgot!
But it's amazing! It's a bigger tie than the last one.
I forgot! Congratulations!
It's tiny!
That's all right, it's just a tie.
About 15 centimetres?
A little over 20 cm.
Beautiful.
The blue eyeshadow is beautiful.
We're all happy.
Here it is.
We did it!
I've caught two fish and I'm going home.
I'll drive everyone home safely.
Yeah! Let's go home.
There are a lot of pikes in this area, so if we hit one, we'll be in big trouble.
I'm scared.
When I got my licence, I took Tokyo.
There were no obstacles at all.
But my hometown is full of obstacles.
I'm scared.
I prefer driving a boat to driving a car.
It's so much more comfortable.
I get carsick, but I've never been seasick.
That's why I prefer boats.
It suits me better.
Wait a minute, how did you do that?
That's amazing.
Oh, no.
Scary, scary, scary, scary, scary.
No, it's like this all the time.
This is how they always speed up so much.
It slows me down.
I like to take it easy.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
What? Are you okay?
We're approaching the exit.
After fishing, after fishing.
After fishing.
How was the fishing?
It's a bit frustrating, really.
I'll show you the fish I caught today.
Here you go.
Grouper and...
A sea bream.
Tiny.
It's a bit frustrating, really.
I only caught a few tiny fish.
I wanted to catch something over 50 centimetres.
I was more like...
I was trying to lure the fish in.
I wanted to use some kind of technique to lure the fish in, but...
But I was told not to touch the fish, and they were very strict.
I was only testing my luck, and I ended up not having much luck.
Thank you very much.
I'm home.
What shall we name him?
I want to grow up.
I want to be big.
I want to be big, I want to be big.
I'll start with the scales.
Take off the scales!
Wow!
I almost got a scale stuck in my hand.
Here you go...
I want to be big, boy.
Did you get all the scales?
It looks like they've been removed.
Cut off the head.
It's clean now.
Then I'll press it into three pieces.
Did you know they're still tiny?
It happens, too, that this is the first time I've ever cut a tiny little tasseled tai.
Will there be any fruit left?
Please let them stay.
I'm sorry I'm late, but...
I'm thinking of making carpaccio with it.
It's cut.
It looks like this.
Three pieces.
That's a lot of food, but still not much.
I must have caught a small one.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Wow!
I've got a really nice skin.
I did it!
And then...
Let's get the middle bone.
Yes.
Put the liver leaf on it.
We're on the prairie.
And not the sauce, not the broth.
What do you call it?
Dressing.
I'll make it.
One tablespoon of olive oil.
One? Half a tablespoon? A pinch?
A pinch of salt?
How much is a handful?
A handful.
About this much?
Yes, it's good for a while.  Put some black pepper on it.
A lot, like this, like this, like this.
And cut up the washed tomatoes.
Tomatoes.
Yes, yes.
All right, we'll rinse them and cut them.
Who's that? Who pinched this tiny hand?
I did.
Finally, pour this dressing over it.
And voila, it's done.
Item 1 - Thai carpaccio.
I'd like to cook the grouper.
This is my first time cooking grouper.
Does she have scales?
Oh, yes! Is that normal?
Mr. Hatasan!
Hata-san? We have to decide on a name for you, too.
Hata-san...
How about Evata-san?
How's Evata-san? Evata-san, Evata-san...
I'm going to find her.
We'll have to film in the light.
Okay, let's start with the image processing.
I'll start with the image processing.
Okay, we've cleaned it up.
And then...
And then salt.
Put salt on it.
Let it sit for 15 minutes.
After a while.
It's not quite cooked through.
Cut a slit in it.
Oh, shit.
Give it to Evatos.
Batten down the hatches.
Hot water.
Is it called a simferi?
Simferi?
A little hot water.
To get rid of the smell.
It's a contraption.
It's like this.
A little bit of powder that's been tidied up.
I'll put it in ice water.
I'll try to remove some of the slime.
Put two tablespoons
Put two tablespoons of sugar in the pan.
120ml of water.
And 120ml of alcohol.
120ml.
2 tablespoons merrin
2 tablespoons soy sauce 2 tablespoons soy sauce
I'm going to put Mr Evatto in.
Evato!
It went in with a bang!
It smells so good!
I'm going to serve more.
Fish-shaped.
For your father and mother's wedding.
From the wedding.
It's a wedding present.
Cute!
Good luck!
It's done!
I don't know, thanks to the plate.
It looks like a very expensive fish.
Looks delicious.
With Miss Evata.
I want to grow up!
Thank you for the food.
Yay!
Looks so delicious!
They both turned out great!
Yay!
I'm going to try the Thai kalpacha.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Oh, it's delicious.
Deliciously sweet, deliciously sweet.
It's delicious.
That's all.